Hi there, I'm Mat Leonard.
مرحبًا، أنا Mat Leonard.
I'll be your instructor for this course on data visualization.
سأكون معلمكم في هذه الدورة التدريبية المخصصة لعرض البيانات.
Where you'll be learning how to create graphics for exploring data and
حيث ستتعلمون كيفية إنشاء الرسومات واستكشاف البيانات
sharing your results.
ومشاركة النتائج.
When we're talking about data visualization,
عندما نتحدث عن عرض البيانات،
we mean the visual display of quantitative information.
نعني العرض البصري للبيانات الكمية.
It's the name of this book, Edward Tufte's seminal work.
إنه اسم هذا الكتاب، العمل الأساسي للكاتب Edward Tufte.
This thing is beautiful and it's essential for
هذا العمل رائع وضروري
anyone interested in database.
لأي شخص مهتم بقواعد البيانات.
If this isn't enough an endorsement, maybe President Obama can convince you.
إذا لم يكن هذا كافيا لإقناعكم، ربما يستطيع الرئيس أوباما إقناعكم.
Use visualizations to tell a story.
استخدموا المرئيات في أخبار قصة.
Here's a graph showing the number of times have been attacked from my evil
إليكم رسم يوضح عدد المرات التي هاجمتني فيها قطتي
kitten Chihiro.
الشريرة Chihiro.
I've made a data points pictures of my face indicating how much pain I was in.
لقد أنشأت نقاط البيانات بصور لوجهي تعبر عن كمية الألم الذي كنت أعانيه.
What's the story here?
ما القصة هنا؟
Tuesday was a rough day for me.
يوم الثلاثاء كان يومًا عصيبًا عليّ.
Wednesday was pretty great, and Chihero is a tiny tiger occupying my home.
يوم الأربعاء كان رائعًا، واحتلّت Chihero منزلي.
In this course, you'll learn how to design and create visualizations.
في هذه الدورة التدريبية، ستتعلمون كيف تقومون بتصميم وإنشاء المرئيات.
First, I'll cover fundamentals and design principles.
أولًا، سأغطي الأساسيات ومبادئ التصميم.
Then, you'll learn how to actually make visualizations.
بعد ذلك، ستتعلمون كيفية إنشاء المرئيات.
Let's get started.
لنبدأ.